{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071797509","data":{"timestamp":" 948071797509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071802237","data":{"timestamp":" 948071802237"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071809448","data":{"timestamp":" 948071809447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL2.incr.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071817509","data":{"timestamp":" 948071817509"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071823360","data":{"timestamp":" 948071823360"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071830290","data":{"timestamp":" 948071830289"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071836905","data":{"timestamp":" 948071836905"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071847193","data":{"timestamp":" 948071847192"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071856119","data":{"timestamp":" 948071856119"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071859459","data":{"timestamp":" 948071859459"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071863053","data":{"timestamp":" 948071863053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071866964","data":{"timestamp":" 948071866964"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071870866","data":{"timestamp":" 948071870866"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071876769","data":{"timestamp":" 948071876769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071880576","data":{"timestamp":" 948071880575"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071884990","data":{"timestamp":" 948071884990"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071889300","data":{"timestamp":" 948071889300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071893305","data":{"timestamp":" 948071893304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071897267","data":{"timestamp":" 948071897267"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071900546","data":{"timestamp":" 948071900546"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071904015","data":{"timestamp":" 948071904014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071908469","data":{"timestamp":" 948071908469"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071912091","data":{"timestamp":" 948071912091"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071916436","data":{"timestamp":" 948071916436"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071921429","data":{"timestamp":" 948071921428"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071926473","data":{"timestamp":" 948071926473"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071930478","data":{"timestamp":" 948071930478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071935386","data":{"timestamp":" 948071935386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071938871","data":{"timestamp":" 948071938871"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071943198","data":{"timestamp":" 948071943198"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071947025","data":{"timestamp":" 948071947024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071953562","data":{"timestamp":" 948071953562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071959323","data":{"timestamp":" 948071959322"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 962bd96d-bbb9-4ae3-bc33-2a8625178305"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071968580","data":{"timestamp":" 948071968579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071968809","data":{"timestamp":" 948071968808"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071969788","data":{"timestamp":" 948071969785"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071971083","data":{"timestamp":" 948071971082"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071974009","data":{"timestamp":" 948071974008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071974863","data":{"timestamp":" 948071974863"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071975184","data":{"timestamp":" 948071975184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071976425","data":{"timestamp":" 948071976425"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071979989","data":{"timestamp":" 948071979989"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071980984","data":{"timestamp":" 948071980983"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071981244","data":{"timestamp":" 948071981244"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071982196","data":{"timestamp":" 948071982196"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071985125","data":{"timestamp":" 948071985124"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071986158","data":{"timestamp":" 948071986158"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071986630","data":{"timestamp":" 948071986630"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071991202","data":{"timestamp":" 948071991200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948071991308","data":{"timestamp":" 948071991308"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" e7b823a6-77a0-4ffe-9648-e9165e1de55d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072001325","data":{"timestamp":" 948072001325"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072008114","data":{"timestamp":" 948072008114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlango"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072009728","data":{"timestamp":" 948072009728"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" MKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072013347","data":{"timestamp":" 948072013347"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072014895","data":{"timestamp":" 948072014895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072018260","data":{"timestamp":" 948072018260"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mvua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072019813","data":{"timestamp":" 948072019812"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072024321","data":{"timestamp":" 948072024321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072025870","data":{"timestamp":" 948072025870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072029541","data":{"timestamp":" 948072029541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mamba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072031099","data":{"timestamp":" 948072031099"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072035705","data":{"timestamp":" 948072035705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072037255","data":{"timestamp":" 948072037255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mashua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072040507","data":{"timestamp":" 948072040507"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mashua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072042071","data":{"timestamp":" 948072042071"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpapai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAPAI"," userResponse":" MPAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072045861","data":{"timestamp":" 948072045861"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpapai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072047448","data":{"timestamp":" 948072047447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072051037","data":{"timestamp":" 948072051037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072052600","data":{"timestamp":" 948072052600"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072056306","data":{"timestamp":" 948072056306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072057862","data":{"timestamp":" 948072057862"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMBE"," userResponse":" MWEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072061384","data":{"timestamp":" 948072061384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072062948","data":{"timestamp":" 948072062948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072065818","data":{"timestamp":" 948072065817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mpira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072067373","data":{"timestamp":" 948072067373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchicha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHICHA"," userResponse":" MCHICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072071139","data":{"timestamp":" 948072071139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchicha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHICHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072072701","data":{"timestamp":" 948072072701"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072076045","data":{"timestamp":" 948072076044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" meza"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072077595","data":{"timestamp":" 948072077595"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072081332","data":{"timestamp":" 948072081332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072082887","data":{"timestamp":" 948072082887"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072086841","data":{"timestamp":" 948072086841"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072088395","data":{"timestamp":" 948072088395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072091881","data":{"timestamp":" 948072091881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072093442","data":{"timestamp":" 948072093442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" MSWAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072096969","data":{"timestamp":" 948072096968"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mswaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072098529","data":{"timestamp":" 948072098529"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHOGO"," userResponse":" MUHOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072102122","data":{"timestamp":" 948072102122"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" muhogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUHOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072103684","data":{"timestamp":" 948072103683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072107721","data":{"timestamp":" 948072107721"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072109301","data":{"timestamp":" 948072109301"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" MBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072112176","data":{"timestamp":" 948072112175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072113724","data":{"timestamp":" 948072113724"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072117334","data":{"timestamp":" 948072117334"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072118879","data":{"timestamp":" 948072118879"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072122781","data":{"timestamp":" 948072122780"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072124344","data":{"timestamp":" 948072124343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072127800","data":{"timestamp":" 948072127800"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072129365","data":{"timestamp":" 948072129365"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072133119","data":{"timestamp":" 948072133119"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mikono"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072134678","data":{"timestamp":" 948072134678"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072139367","data":{"timestamp":" 948072139367"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072140830","data":{"timestamp":" 948072140830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072140921","data":{"timestamp":" 948072140921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-M.rand.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072150435","data":{"timestamp":" 948072150434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072150530","data":{"timestamp":" 948072150530"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGUU"," userResponse":" MGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072159711","data":{"timestamp":" 948072159710"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 4d83541e-be22-412b-8f97-6e72c0f0b2a2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-M.rand.52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072170506","data":{"timestamp":" 948072170506"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_j-a-m"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072175377","data":{"timestamp":" 948072175377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_y-m-h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072179980","data":{"timestamp":" 948072179979"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-v-l"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072186656","data":{"timestamp":" 948072186656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_a-m-ch"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072191184","data":{"timestamp":" 948072191184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072192241","data":{"timestamp":" 948072192240"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072198254","data":{"timestamp":" 948072198254"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.103","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072206535","data":{"timestamp":" 948072206534"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_041526"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}